boldmethod.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Boldmethod

We keep your information private. Here's how:

* ## General

At Boldmethod, we respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. Any information that you provide to Boldmethod's Services is subject to our Privacy Policy, which governs our collection and use of your information. You understand that through your use of the Services you consent to the collection and use (as set forth in the Privacy Policy) of this information, including the transfer of this information to our servers for processing and use by Boldmethod. We may collect personally identifiable information when you visit our site, such as your name, email address, and other information. We also may automatically receive and record information on from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page(s) you visited. 

* ## We do not Sell Your Information

We will not sell your personally identifiable information to anyone. 

* ## Cookies And Tracking

We use cookies and tools such as Google Analytics to monitor who views our content and how users engage. Your personal information is kept private, and this information is never sold to third parties. We collect this information to determine which posts are the most engaging, so that we can create more content you'll love. 

We may use Google services, such as AdSense, to display ads on our site; these services use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to our website. Google uses the third-party DoubleClick cookie so that it or its partners can serve ads based on your visits to Boldmethod or other internet sites. You can opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting Google's [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

[Click here to learn how Google uses data when you use their partners' sites or apps.](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)

At times, other third-party vendors and networks may serve ads on Boldmethod and these services may also use third-party cookies. If you'd like to opt-out of these advertisements, you can visit [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

* ## Who can Access Your Information

Boldmethod employees, officers, consultants and other company agents may access your information. In addition, any administrators for Groups you may join may access your information, including data on the progress or results of your training. 

* ## Communications with You

As part of providing you the Services, we may need to provide you with certain communications, such as service announcements and administrative messages. These communications are considered part of the Services and your Boldmethod account, which you may not be able to opt-out from receiving. 

* ## Changes to this Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you via an e-mail to the email associated with your account, or by another method as allowed in the Terms and Conditions. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. 

* ## Contact Information

This privacy policy is operated and provided by Boldmethod, LLC, 2033 11th Street, Suite 2, Boulder, CO 80302. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at [ info@boldmethod.com](mailto:info@boldmethod.com), phone at (720) 663-7754, or by mail at our Boulder address. 

Effective: August 20th, 2014
